<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Twilight Princess Remastered Blog</title>
        <link>https://zelda.fimmel.dev/blog</link>
        <description>Twilight Princess Remastered Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[January 2025]]></title>
            <link>https://zelda.fimmel.dev/blog/updates</link>
            <guid>updates</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Current Development Status]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="current-development-status"><strong>Current Development Status</strong><a class="hash-link" href="#current-development-status" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>We are excited to share the progress of our fan project! Below is a detailed log of updates, new features, and planned improvements.</p><hr><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="changelog"><strong>Changelog</strong><a class="hash-link" href="#changelog" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="january-2025"><strong>January 2025</strong><a class="hash-link" href="#january-2025" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><ul><li><p><strong>Graphics &amp; Visuals</strong>:</p><ul><li>Enhanced lighting system to improve realism and match the original Twilight Princess aesthetic.</li><li>Updated texture resolution for character models, environment assets, and UI elements.</li><li>Added post-processing effects, including bloom and ambient occlusion, for a polished visual experience.</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Gameplay Mechanics</strong>:</p><ul><li>Improved combat system with smoother animations and hit detection.</li><li>Recreated the original horseback riding mechanics for seamless player control.</li><li>Enhanced enemy AI to make encounters more dynamic and challenging.</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Environment &amp; World</strong>:</p><ul><li>Fully remastered Ordon Village with updated geometry, textures, and lighting.</li><li>Improved foliage interaction using Unity's Shader Graph for dynamic vegetation movement.</li><li>Recreated Twilight Realm effects with custom shaders.</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Audio</strong>:</p><ul><li>Remastered background music with high-quality samples inspired by the original soundtrack.</li><li>Implemented 3D positional audio for immersive environmental effects.</li><li>Added voiceover placeholders for key cutscenes.</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>UI Improvements</strong>:</p><ul><li>Redesigned HUD to better match modern resolutions while retaining the original feel.</li><li>Added scalable elements for better support across multiple screen sizes.</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Other Features</strong>:</p><ul><li>Initial implementation of a save/load system for player progress.</li><li>Added a debug menu for internal testing and troubleshooting.</li><li>Optimized game performance for stable framerate across mid-tier hardware.</li></ul></li></ul><hr><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="planned-features"><strong>Planned Features</strong><a class="hash-link" href="#planned-features" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><ul><li>Implementing the Wolf Link transformation mechanics, including new animations and unique abilities.</li><li>Adding side quests and collectibles inspired by the original game.</li><li>Refining cutscenes with dynamic camera angles and character interactions.</li><li>Introducing a photo mode to capture the remastered visuals.</li><li>Exploring multiplayer or co-op functionality for certain segments, depending on demand.</li></ul><hr><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="notes"><strong>Notes</strong><a class="hash-link" href="#notes" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><ul><li><strong>Platforms</strong>: Targeting PC (Windows) as the primary platform, with potential future expansion to mobile devices.</li><li><strong>Release</strong>: No fixed release date yet; the project remains in active development.</li></ul><hr><p>Thank you for your support as we continue to work on this passion project! Stay tuned for more updates.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <author>contact@fimmel.dev (Fimmel)</author>
            <category>updates</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>